Contact

8111 South Emerson Avenue Indianapolis IN 46237 317-528-8133 (Work) susan.mcroberts@comcast.net

www.linkedin.com/in/susanmcroberts-54aa9210 (LinkedIn) www.stfrancishospitals.org (Company)

Top Skills

Nursing Strategic Planning Quality Management

Certifications

Informatics Certificate

Nurse Executive-Advanced

Susan McRoberts

VP/CNO Franciscan Health Central Indiana (retired December 2017) Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Summary

I have long-time experience in clinical leadership and administration, nursing strategic planning and professional practice model development and quality management. Additionally, I have experience teaching nursing leadership at both the undergraduate and graduate levels in a large university setting. I have certifications in nursing leadership (2), Informatics and Health Care Quality. My other professional interests are in public health (disaster preparation and management) and the history of nursing.

My clinical experience is in behavioral health.

Specialties: Nursing strategic planning, clinical resource and productivity management, change leadership, clinical informatics strategic leadership and implementation, professional practice model development, quality management.

Experience

Indiana University School of Nursing Associate Adjunct Professor August 2005 - Present (15 years) Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Graduate-Nursing Administration

Franciscan St. Francis Health
22 years 11 months

VP Patient Care Services and CNO
July 1997 - December 2017 (20 years 6 months)
Indianapolis Indiana

Director of Quality Management February 1995 - June 2000 (5 years 5 months)

Education

Indiana University-Purdue University at Indianapolis MSN, Nursing Administration · (2002 - 2005)

Indiana University Bloomington